Binghamton Central Labor Union Records on Microfilm 5688 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Binghamton Central Labor Union Records on Microfilm
1941-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Binghamton Central Labor Union
5688 mf
0.11 cubic feet
1 microfilm reel
Audiovisual materials, microfilm.
The Binghamton Central Labor Union Records on 183 microfilm reels.
3338526
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Scope and Contents
A negative copy is available upon request.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Binghamton -- Local unions; Agricultural laborers -- Education; Binghamton Central Labor Union (Binghamton, N.Y.)
3338526
- Records, 1941-1960 (Reel 1)
  - Crowley Milk was added to the Central's "we do not patronize" list., 1941; 1 (Reel 1)
    Scope and Contents
    January 7, 1941.
  - Union members were asked not to buy Time and Life, since they were published by an anti-union company., 1941; 2 (Reel 1)
  - Members were asked not to patronize non-union bars., 1941; 3 (Reel 1)
  - Binghamton Central Labor Council (BCLU) endorses AFL opposition to anti-strike legislation of Senator Smith (of Virginia)., 1941; 4 (Reel 1)
    January 8, 1941.
  - BCLU wrote to state senators, favoring the lowering the minimum age for old age support., 1941; 5 (Reel 1)
    February 19, 1941.
  - BCLU and Operating Engineers Local 410 offer financial support to striking bus drivers., 1941; 6 (Reel 1)
    June 4, 1941.
  - Additional financial support for the striking drivers was made by union carpenters, pressmen, and printers., 1941; 7 (Reel 1)
    June 18, 1941.
  - Since no city workers are in Civil Service or receiving a scale of wages equal to union scale, it was resolved, to ask for salary increase for these workers., 1941; 8 (Reel 1)
    September 3, 1941.
  - Efforts to get International Garment Workers representative in the area to organize was announced., 1941; 9 (Reel 1)
  - Names and addresses of appropriate workers needing organizing were requested., 1941; 10 (Reel 1)
  - The effort to get the chauffeurs into BCLU was reported upon., 1941; 11 (Reel 1)
  - A committee was appointed for the purpose of bringing the chauffeurs into the BCLU., 1941; 12 (Reel 1)
    October 1, 1941.
  - Chauffeurs join the BCLU with a unanimous vote., 1941; 13 (Reel 1)
    October 15, 1941.
  - The same committee that organized the chauffeurs will attempt to recruit the hotel and restaurant employees as well as the photographic and chemical workers., 1941; 14 (Reel 1)
  - It was reported that Beiber Isaccs, Gen. Managers, was building a home under unfair conditions. The BCLU's Housing Committee promised to investigate., 1941; 15 (Reel 1)
  - A committee is formed to combat the new tax on amusement places using live as opposed to recorded band music., 1941; 16 (Reel 1)
    November 5, 1941.
  - A committee is formed to investigate the Workers Defense League and its efforts to seek the release from jail of Kephler and Gilmore of the Teamsters Local., 1941; 17 (Reel 1)
    November 19, 1941.
  - A committee was formed to decide on whether or not the BCLU should draw up resolutions to be sent to the Governor requesting Kephler and Gilmore's release., 1941; 18 (Reel 1)
  - Telegrams are sent by BCLU, upon the request of President Green, to Congressmen and Senators expressing their opposition to H.R. 6075., 1941; 19 (Reel 1)
    December 3, 1941.
  - E. Kephler of the Teamsters Local to be released soon, after which resolutions will be sent for the release of Carl Gilmore., 1941; 20 (Reel 1)
  - Ten dollar donation by the Council to be used to fight Infantile Paralysis by the President's Labor Committee., 1942; 21 (Reel 1)
    January 21, 1942.
  - It was announced that Budweiser beer truck drivers are non-union. BCLU members asked not to buy Bud., 1942; 22 (Reel 1)
    February 18, 1942.
  - Committee formed to try and get the photo and chemical workers to join BCLU., 1942; 23 (Reel 1)
    March 4, 1942.
  - Communication sent to Binghamton press protesting it's anti-labor attitude., 1942; 24 (Reel 1)
    March 18, 1942.
  - New York State AFL requests that BCLU send letters to State Senators and Assemblymen endorsing Governor Lehman's recommendations., 1942; 25 (Reel 1)
    April 1, 1942. Recommendation are to 1) increase maximum unemployment benefit period from 13 to 20 weeks. 2) reduce waiting period from 3 weeks. 3) extend from the minimum of 7 to a maximum of 18 dollars.
  - Brother Morey was sent to aid the striking Upholsterers Union., 1942; 26 (Reel 1)
    April 15, 1942.
  - BCLU members are asked not to patronize non-union grills and barber shops., 1942; 27 (Reel 1)
  - Five dollars are donated to the Blind Work Association., 1942; 28 (Reel 1)
    May 6, 1942.
  - Six dollars are donated to the Disabled American Veterans., 1942; 29 (Reel 1)
    June 3, 1942.
  - Five dollars are donated to the Veterans of Foreign Wars., 1942; 30 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU aids local blacks to develop housing project., 1942; 31 (Reel 1)
    September 2, 1942.
  - Organization attempts are made at Ozalid Products Co., 1942; 32 (Reel 1)
  - Sweet's Foundry becomes a union shop., 1942; 33 (Reel 1)
  - City firemen affiliate with the BCLU., 1942; 34 (Reel 1)
    October 7, 1942.
  - Organization attempts made at Afqa-Ansco are met with resistance., 1942; 35 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU endorses the Blood Bank and encourages members to give., 1942; 36 (Reel 1)
    October 21, 1942.
  - Roofers organized. Photo and chemical workers refuse to affiliate., 1942; 37 (Reel 1)
    November 4, 1942.
  - Five dollars are donated to the Blind Workers., 1942; 38 (Reel 1)
    November 18, 1942.
  - Chauffeurs state they will withdraw from the BCLU., 1942; 39 (Reel 1)
    December 2, 1942.
  - BCLU endorses Paul Spendley for Binghamton Post Master., 1942; 40 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU endorses R. Segmore for state Industrial Commissioner., 1942; 41 (Reel 1)
  - Servicemen and pensioners who are not paying dues are determined to be exempt from the per capita tax., 1942; 42 (Reel 1)
  - A "Labor Council" is formed which consists of local unions from the CIO, Independent, and non-affiliated A.F.L. organizations. The purpose of the Council is to combat anti-labor legislation., 1943; 43 (Reel 1)
    February 13, 1943.
  - BCLU agrees to help the Red Cross on an upcoming project in any way it can., 1943; 44 (Reel 1)
    February 17, 1943.
  - Per capita tax of the BCLU is lowered to ten cents for a trial period., 1943; 45 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU makes plans to set up an educational program on labor problems through radio broadcasts and the local daily newspapers., 1943; 46 (Reel 1)
    March 6, 1943.
  - A committee is established to investigate the possibility of having a fair, circus, or bazaar to raise funds for BCLU., 1943; 47 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU asked for assistance by local Bartenders Union in its grievance with the Bingham Hotel., 1943; 48 (Reel 1)
    March 20, 1943. BCLU sends a letter to management of hotel requesting that management meet the bartenders' demands.
  - Five dollars is sent to Sheltered Workshop Foundation., 1943; 49 (Reel 1)
    April 7, 1943.
  - Five dollars is donated to the Blind Association., 1943; 50 (Reel 1)
    May 5, 1943.
  - Attempts to organize the Dry Back Corp. are announced., 1943; 51 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU organizes a congressional letter writing campaign in opposition to the Connelly bill., 1943; 52 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU supports the Hotel and Waitresses' Local Union in an organizing drive., 1943; 53 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU decides to rent space in their new building to the general public., 1943; 54 (Reel 1)
    July 10, 1943.
  - BCLU plans its Labor Day Celebration., 1943; 55 (Reel 1)
    July 17, 1943.
  - Card of bereavement sent to the family of the late Bro. Paul Baker of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union., 1943; 56 (Reel 1)
    October 6, 1943.
  - BCLU endorses Wm. S. Richardson for city judge., 1943; 57 (Reel 1)
    October 20, 1943.
  - Five dollars is donated to Blind Association., 1943; 58 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU petitions against the reestablishment of Prohibition., 1943; 59 (Reel 1)
    December 15, 1943.
  - BCLU involved in distribution of Christmas baskets and dinners; the BCLU also donate $10 to the project., 1943; 60 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU makes efforts to get law extending firemen's working hours vetoed., 1944; 61 (Reel 1)
    January 10, 1944.
  - BCLU assists in Red Cross blood drive., 1944; 62 (Reel 1)
    March 15, 1944.
  - The Council writes the appropriate political figures opposing the 30% amusement tax in bar and clubs that has been putting musicians out of work., 1944; 63 (Reel 1)
  - Five hundred dollars is donated to Blind Work Association., 1944; 64 (Reel 1)
    May 17, 1944.
  - Members are urged to buy "All American" Union cigarettes., 1944; 65 (Reel 1)
  - Six dollars is given to Bro. Lundy of Painters' Union, suffering from serious illness., 1944; 66 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU publicly denies communist infiltration, 1944; 67 (Reel 1)
    June 21, 1944. Renounces "revolutionary and radical movements" after being linked to the American Labor Party and CIO Political Action Committee, "members of which...were alleged to have Communistic backgrounds."
  - Committee organized to study possibilities for Labor College scholarship., 1944; 68 (Reel 1)
    July 5, 1944.
  - Returning servicemen not to be charged any local fees for joining unions., 1944; 69 (Reel 1)
    November 15, 1944.
  - The Municipal - Street and Electric Railway Employees #1145 and Sheet Metal Workers #112 granted charters., 1944; 70 (Reel 1)
  - Ten dollars is donated to Red Cross., 1945; 71 (Reel 1)
    March 7, 1945.
  - Five dollars is donated to Sheltered Workshop Foundation., 1945; 72 (Reel 1)
    March 21, 1945.
  - Local 218 of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union affiliates., 1945; 73 (Reel 1)
    April 4, 1945.
  - Electricians Local #325 affiliates., 1945; 74 (Reel 1)
    April 18, 1945.
  - BCLU joins the AFL in its observation of National Citizenship Day., 1945; 75 (Reel 1)
  - All requests for donations will be returned if they do not bear the Union printing label., 1945; 76 (Reel 1)
  - Five dollars donated to the Blind Association., 1945; 77 (Reel 1)
    May 16, 1945.
  - ANSCO workers affiliates with the BCLU., 1945; 78 (Reel 1)
    June 20, 1945.
  - BCLU "goes on record" as being in total support, and "doing all they can" to establish physical education programs in all schools., 1945; 79 (Reel 1)
  - Brewery Workers Local affiliates with the BCLU., 1945; 80 (Reel 1)
    July 14, 1945.
  - BCLU observes National Physical Handicap Week., 1945; 81 (Reel 1)
    September 19, 1945.
  - BCLU donates to Community and War Chests., 1945; 82 (Reel 1)
    October 3, 1945.
  - Five dollars is donated to Blind Workers Association., 1946; 83 (Reel 1)
    June 5, 1946.
  - BCLU supports entertainment program., 1946; 84 (Reel 1)
    June 19, 1946.
  - BCLU supports Minimum Wage and Fair Employment Practices bills, as well as Anti-Poll Tax Bill., 1946; 85 (Reel 1)
    September 4, 1946.
  - ANSCO Machinists affiliate., 1946; 86 (Reel 1)
    November 6, 1946.
  - Five dollars is donated to Guiding Eyes, Inc., 1946; 87 (Reel 1)
    November 20, 1946.
  - Infantile Paralysis fund raiser nets $329.50., 1947; 88 (Reel 1)
    February 5, 1947.
  - Twenty five dollars is donated to the Sheltered Work Shop., 1947; 89 (Reel 1)
    March 5, 1947.
  - Local 112 of the Plumbers and Steamfitters affiliates., 1947; 90 (Reel 1)
    March 19, 1947.
  - BCLU supports United Leather Workers International Union in its attempts to organize Endicott-Johnson workers., 1947; 91 (Reel 1)
    April 16, 1947.
  - BCLU members are requested to buy shares in local cooperative stores., 1947; 92 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU formerly supports bus operators should they strike., 1947; 93 (Reel 1)
    May 7, 1947.
  - Entire BCLU body goes to waitresses picket after meeting for one hour of picket duty., 1947; 94 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU writes congressmen in effort to increase postal department budget., 1947; 95 (Reel 1)
  - Aid given to Waitresses Union in their strike., 1947; 96 (Reel 1)
    May 31, 1947.
  - Five dollars is donated to Blind Work Association., 1947; 97 (Reel 1)
    June 4, 1947.
  - Gains are reported in the bus operators strike., 1947; 98 (Reel 1)
  - The Postal Clerks and the Chemical Workers affiliate., 1947; 99 (Reel 1)
    June 18, 1947.
  - Striking Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees are aided by the BCLU., 1947; 100 (Reel 1)
    July 16, 1947.
  - BCLU seeks joint action with C.I.O. in opposition to the Taft- Hartley Bill., 1947; 101 (Reel 1)
    September 3, 1947.
  - BCLU donates $100.00 to the Labor Education Committee., 1947; 102 (Reel 1)
    November 5, 1947.
  - BCLU donates $100.00 to the Labor Education Committee., 1947; 103 (Reel 1)
    November 19, 1947.
  - BCLU goes on record opposing the Taft-Hartley Law and politicians who support it, calling it "slave labor legislation", 1948; 104 (Reel 1)
    February 4, 1948.
  - BCLU speaks out against the distribution of "obnoxious" National Association of Manufacturers (NAM) literature in schools., 1948; 105 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU donates $10 to National Farm Union., 1948; 106 (Reel 1)
    January 21, 1948.
  - BCLU/CIO Joint Pac give "unqualified support" to ITU in its struggle in Chicago., 1948; 107 (Reel 1)
    January 7, 1948.
  - BCLU urges enactment of legislation (in NY State) to give financial support to cerebral palsy victims and to cerebral palsy research centers., 1948; 108 (Reel 1)
    February 23, 1948. A resolution to this effect is sent to Governor Dewey, and Binghamton area Senators and Assemblymen.
  - BCLU affiliates with AFL Workers Education Bureau of America., 1948; 109 (Reel 1)
    March 17,1948.
  - BCLU protests to area Board of Educations over the distribution in the schools of "vicious" NAM pamphlets., 1948; 110 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU donates $100 to Locals 173 and 218 of the Hotel and Bartenders International Union for strike assistance at the Arlington Hotel., 1948; 111 (Reel 1)
    May 5, 1948.
  - BCLU goes on record in support of John L. Lewis and United Mine Workers., 1948; 112 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU committee assigned to meet with Arlington Hotel management., 1948; 113 (Reel 1)
    April 7, 1948.
  - BCLU goes on record as opposing the Mundt-Nixon Bill., 1948; 114 (Reel 1)
    June 2, 1948.
  - BCLU establishes a Blood Bank Center at the BCLU., 1948; 115 (Reel 1)
    July 7, 1948.
  - BCLU donates $1500 to National Women's Trade Union League., 1948; 116 (Reel 1)
    November 17, 1948.
  - BCLU pledges $1800 to Lourdes Hospital Building Fund., 1949; 117 (Reel 1)
    May 18, 1949.
  - BCLU donates $100 to the Boys Club., 1949; 118 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU donates $25 to the National Cancer Foundation., 1949; 119 (Reel 1)
    July 6, 1949.
  - BCLU donates $25 to Community Chest., 1949; 120 (Reel 1)
    August 17, 1949.
  - Chauffeurs and Teamsters Local #693 affiliates with BCLU., 1949; 121 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU donates $100 to the Salvation Army., 1949; 122 (Reel 1)
    November 2, 1949.
  - BCLU donates $64.61 to Moon Building fire victims; a committee and fund is established for the same cause., 1949; 123 (Reel 1)
    December 21, 1949.
  - BCLU to organize a Samuel Gompers celebration., 1950; 124 (Reel 1)
    March 1, 1950.
  - BCLU offers time to assist the local division of Girl Scouts of America., 1950; 125 (Reel 1)
    May 17, 1950.
  - BCLU supports H.R. 647, to establish a Department of Health, Education, and Security., 1950; 126 (Reel 1)
    July 5, 1950.
  - BCLU donates $100 to the Boys Club., 1950; 127 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU actively supports the reelection of Senator Lehman., 1950; 128 (Reel 1)
    October 18, 1950.
  - BCLU requests its members not to patronize a local, non-union bar., 1950; 129 (Reel 1)
    May 2, 1951.
  - BCLU supports Chemical Workers Union in their difficulties at Ansco., 1950; 130 (Reel 1)
    July 12, 1951.
  - BCLU supports Prudential Insurance agents in their strike., 1952; 131 (Reel 1)
    January 11, 1952.
  - BCLU Executive Committee endorses a sales tax to give cost-of-living adjustments to city employees., 1952; 132 (Reel 1)
    April 14, 1952.
  - It is announced that the Teamsters Union, a BCLU affiliate, has donated an iron lung to Lourdes Hospital., 1952; 133 (Reel 1)
    August 20, 1952.
  - Mayor Kramer is endorsed for reelection., 1953; 134 (Reel 1)
    October 21, 1953.
  - The International Chemical Workers Union affiliate., 1953; 135 (Reel 1)
    December 2, 1953.
  - BCLU officially supports Musicians Union in its dispute with the Vestal Legion; the Vestal Legion Hall is boycotted., 1954; 136 (Reel 1)
    April 7, 1954.
  - BCLU officially supports the Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union is its dispute with Spaulding Bakeries., 1954; 137 (Reel 1)
    May 5, 1954.
  - A formal letter stating the BCLU's support of the Teachers Federation in its dispute with the Binghamton Board of Education is sent to the appropriate parties., 1954; 138 (Reel 1)
    May 16, 1954.
  - BCLU donates five dollars to the International Guiding Eyes Inc., 1954; 139 (Reel 1)
    August 18, 1954.
  - The Teamsters affiliate with BCLU., 1954; 140 (Reel 1)
    September 1, 1954.
  - BCLU supports the Plumbers and Steamfitters in their dispute with Ansco., 1954; 141 (Reel 1)
    October 6, 1954.
  - BCLU suspends their dues and gives free meeting space to distressed Garment Workers., 1954; 142 (Reel 1)
    December 15, 1954.
  - Brother Whitley addresses 35 seniors at Union-Endicott High School on "Why Collective Bargaining?", 1955; 143 (Reel 1)
    March 2, 1955.
  - BCLU endorses appointment of Mrs. Victoria Levent to the NYS Anti-Discrimination Commission., 1955; 144 (Reel 1)
    May 18, 1955.
  - BCLU supports Amalgamated Meat Cutters efforts in organizing Endicott-Johnson's Fur and Leather Division., 1955; 145 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU goes on record supporting a NYS seven and one half million dollar bond issue to build roads., 1955; 146 (Reel 1)
    September 7, 1955.
  - BCLU unanimously endorses strike vote by Traction Co. Bus Operators., 1955; 147 (Reel 1)
    December 7, 1955.
  - BCLU places Elks Club on its unfair list for firing Musicians Union members who refused to cross a Bartenders picket., 1955; 148 (Reel 1)
  - President Maurice Quain sent as BCLU delegate to AF of L- CIO Unity Convention., 1955; 149 (Reel 1)
    December 21, 1955.
  - With help from BCLU, Local 263 of Beer Drivers, Brewery, Soft Drink and Maintenance Workers, organize Lucas Distributing Company, Donnelly Distributing Company, and Canada Dry Bottle Co., 1956; 150 (Reel 1)
    January 4,1956.
  - BCLU appoint representatives to the Citizens' Committee for construction of Veterans' Memorial Auditorium., 1956; 151 (Reel 1)
  - BCLU donates ten dollars to the Westinghouse Strike Fund., 1956; 152 (Reel 1)
    March 7, 1956.
  - At the request of Retail Clerks, Binghamton Montgomery Ward is placed on the Council's "Do Not Patronize" list., 1956; 153 (Reel 1)
    May 16, 1956.
  - Contract negotiation completed between Retail Clerks and Montgomery Ward. Ward's is taken off "Do Not Patronize" list., 1956; 154 (Reel 1)
    November 7, 1956.
  - BCLU supports N.A.B.E.T. in their strike against Triangle Publications Inc. (WNBF)., 1956; 155 (Reel 1)
    December 5, 1956.
  - On the request of the AFL, the BCLU voices protest over Soviet acts in Hungary., 1956; 156 (Reel 1)
    December 19, 1956.
  - Iron Workers affiliate., 1956; 157 (Reel 1)
  - "Sunshine gift" sent to Bro. Bernard Whitley who's sick in the hospital., 1957; 158 (Reel 1)
    January 2, 1957.
  - Crowley's Milk Co. placed on BCLU's "unfair list"., 1957; 159 (Reel 1)
    January 16, 1957.
  - BCLU supports the NABET in their strike against WNBF-TV's facilities., 1957; 160 (Reel 1)
    July 17, 1957. Also notify all local unions of strike and organize mass picketing.
  - Unions chartered by newly merged AFL-CIO in the BCLU, 1957; 161 (Reel 1)
    October 25, 1957. Includes: Bricklayers, Masons & Plasterers, Local 42; Journey Bakers, Local #156; Bakery & Confectionary Workers, Local #354; Electrical Workers, Local #325; Insurance Agents International Union, Local #139; Hod Carriers, Building & Com
  - BCLU officially endorses John J. Burns for election to the post of Mayor of Binghamton., 1957; 162 (Reel 1)
    October 25, 1957.
  - BCLU is rezoned by the AFL-CIO and renamed to Broome-East Tioga Federation of Labor. (BFL), 1957; 163 (Reel 1)
  - BFL allows its hall to be used as polling place for Congressional elections., 1957; 164 (Reel 1)
    December l8, 1957.
  - BFL assists the Teachers Federation in its membership drive., 1958; 165 (Reel 1)
    April 2, 1958.
  - BFL plans for establishment of a permanent labor library at local Labor Temple., 1958; 166 (Reel 1)
    April 16, 1958.
  - Letters of protest sent to Westover Branch of the First City National Bank in regard to its displaying of scab-made Kohler products., 1958; 167 (Reel 1)
    May 7, 1958.
  - Foster and Bradley Hotel refuses to recognize the organization attempts of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union., 1958; 168 (Reel 1)
    June 5, 1958.
  - The hotel is given two weeks until it's put on the "we do not patronize list"., 1958; 169 (Reel 1)
  - Postal Clerks Local #858 affiliates., 1958; 170 (Reel 1)
    June 25, 1958.
  - Mayor Burns proclaims Union Label Week., 1958; 171 (Reel 1)
    September 17, 1958.
  - BFL requests pay raise and increased vacation time for Binghamton city employees from City Council., 1958; 172 (Reel 1)
    November 4, 1958.
  - BFL places Stroehmann's Bread and Proctor Electrical Appliances on its "We Do Not Patronize" list for employing non-union workers., 1959; 173 (Reel 1)
    January 21, 1959.
  - BFL places AFL-CIO News subscriptions for: Central and North High Schools, Public Library, Harpur College Library, Broome Technical Institute Library, and Seton Catholic High School., 1959; 174 (Reel 1)
    February 25,1959.
  - BFL hosts Peruvian labor leaders., 1959; 175 (Reel 1)
    November 4, 1959.
  - BFL voices its support of the United Packinghouse Workers in their strike against Wilson and Co., 1960; 176 (Reel 1)
    February 3, 1960.
  - BFL puts Wilson and Co. on the "We Do Not Patronize" list., 1960; 177 (Reel 1)
  - BFL asks its local affiliates to write to their senators and assemblymen in opposition to the Pierce-Mason bill., 1960; 178 (Reel 1)
  - BLF delegates write their congressmen urging passage of the Forand Bill., 1960; 179 (Reel 1)
    March 2, 1960.
  - BFL donates money to the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding strike fund., 1960; 180 (Reel 1)
    April 20, 1960.
  - BFL decides to set up a local Union Label and Service Trades Council., 1960; 181 (Reel 1)
    September 7, 1960.
  - BFL supports Postal Clerk's Union by not patronizing Sears and Roebuck., 1960; 182 (Reel 1)
    December 7, 1960.
  - BFL endorses the aims of March of Dimes polio drive., 1960; 183 (Reel 1)
    December 21, 1960.